Everybody, do you hear this song? Do you want to hear this song? Do you hear this song?
Everybody wanted pieces of me
Consumes how applause
Watched fake Kings rehearsed there
With a signal comes a secret
Knows my fate without hinges
Smiles upon
Hi sweetheart, how are you?
How the hell, I can't hear you.
Can you hear me?
Hola!
Oh, now I can hear you.
Okay, good.
Wait, now I can't hear you.
Oh my gosh, what's going on? This is a pickle. Yeah, let me leave it for that. Okay. Come back in the meantime
I'll put I'll find something to play. Hold on. Let me see. Here's a big piece of. Oh, here. Oh rain is back. Rain
There we go. You hear me now? Yep. Yeah, how are you?
I'm good. How are you? Hey look there's booty goon is in the chat
They showed Joe
Yeah, I showed some of the new pictures. Do you see the new pictures that um, that um, um our friend
Uh, I think they were Bakelips did
No, I don't know who that is. I don't know who any of these people are psyche. What's the fuck?
Oh my gosh, Bakelips is new. So Bakelips is a big fat guy, but he's actually, I mean he's done really offensive
pictures of me, but he has really funny ones
of like Bita and other people.
And so I kind of just keep forgiving him.
He's probably at my mod half the time.
Why are we wasting our time with these people?
I don't know, but you know what?
I'm gonna show you a big close to these pictures
and then you're gonna understand, okay?
What the hell, did you get a perm?
Like why is your hair so curly?
I did a Sandman, I did a Sandman perm.
Ew, Sandman is ugly.
in fact
This guy on you want to see them again on yeah, we can see them again. They're seeing this picture of Sam and
Look at this picture
Yeah, I think sure of me looks fine. Oh, this one right here. She looks good. Look
It's a man beta
That's a real photo. What's wrong Sam and ugly as fuck. What the fuck? I'm sorry. I'm sorry
Sam and me. I'm not trying to be mean. I'm not advertising me. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I'm not trying to be mean
I'm not. I didn't even it's like he fell out of the ugly tree and hit every branch on the way down. Yeah. I mean, okay
We do have okay. Okay. I can show you Joe's pictures. Yeah, hold on. I hope I don't want to go shapely
Yeah, I have Joe shapely's picture. Oh
You like you like to even that guy he's bald
Yeah, he's he's a bald ginger
He looks like 500 pounds of bird shit. Yeah, let's show
Oh, so you know him? You met him?
I've seen him before.
We had a guest coming up. Who wants to talk to you?
He would show up with this fucking messed up wife or something. I don't know.
Great. I guess he wants to meet you.
Who?
Can I stop?
Oh, I know him.
Hi, how are you?
Oh, hang on. I can't hear you. Let me come back.
I don't know where did she go I don't know where but you know what I just want to ask
you about branding Q what would you have to say about Branding Q?
Branding Q, tell us what Branding Q did to you.
So can you hear me come back? What the fuck? Well? Yeah. Well
Well, you hear me
Yes, what what a break you do you?
Why do you why do you want to know? I'm good. Everyone's really curious. We're really concerned about you
Even psyche
He told me to show me
You're me his you know what oh my god. Yeah, okay. I'm so sorry Noel
No, you're saying you're saying Brandon here charge you like
Sexually assault you yes. Oh my god. That's so messed up
Yeah, he a Brandon Q is not a good
He's
Yeah
He really wants me to show me a show a show me. He really wants me to show me
Don't show them. No, I just don't show them. Okay, you don't want to say I won't thank you so much. Oh, yeah
Guys, this is really, this is really a dog.
He's so creepy. What's his thoughts?
It's real creepy.
Girl, who is this girl? I don't know her.
This is Ray. Meet Ray. This is Noelle.
Hi, Noelle.
Hi, do you remember me?
Yeah, I do. You went to JC one time.
Or a couple times.
Are you okay with me?
Why wouldn't I be? I don't really know you.
Okay.
Did you know she was on a show?
She's not supposed to do that.
We totally said no.
And that's supposed to do that.
No, if I don't.
No.
Sorry.
Yeah, don't do that. Yeah, cuz then you get creepy dives like, yeah
Hi, Mr. Noel wasn't that wasn't my dad my dad's bed
Is that your boyfriend?
You
four people that get chosen are getting told.
Hey, she's over there!
She said that's her dad.
Shut up!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my gosh, thank you.
I think we have a lawsuit.
Oh, hang on, I can't hear you.
Okay, darn it.
Okay, hold on once again.
I got Rain back once again.
Rain I'm trying to show you. You know, I'm trying to show you something
I think I finally figured how to show it. Let me figure it out. Let me see that watch that watch before
It was so good. Oh, it's okay. Hold on. Okay. Hold on one second. It was uh, okay
See, I think it's this one
hmm
Hold on it's cartoon
It's so good. If I can show this to you, I would be very happy to it. Why is there a bald guy in the background?
You know, you know how I feel about bald guys. That's thing that is
Yeah, I don't like him. He's bald. Uh-huh. I have a song about him, but
Don't show it because I don't want to see his bald head like his bald ugly shiny head
She's speaking on you
Ball people pissed me off, dude
Okay, well, okay, so I'll show this to you, but hold one second
No, don't show me because I don't want to see both people
It's a different thing
They're fucking immoral
Do you want to watch something about?
The the real minds I can blow your mind. It don't be offended by it, but I can play your mind
Some other day
Okay, I'll love it. It's my day, but you know what in the meantime, I'm gonna blow your mind right now
Uh, hold on one second.
Why is there a snake in your bathroom?
Because that's my best friend baby snake. Hold on one second.
So I have, I have actually something to show you,
and this tells the truth about the world.
Here, whatever the truth about the world,
I know you have. Hold on one second.
Yeah, I don't want to watch your video.
Okay, you don't have to. You can go. You can go.
No.
I want to hang out it's about this is about the Mayan so if you don't like it
But I want to hang out with you. What's the fuck you are you're right here with me. Watch this
You're gonna love this
My it's called Constance. Okay. Well, then hold my hand. I'm gonna hold you. Yeah, we're here together
Okay, we're here together friends, bro like bro like you're gonna freak me out stop next to you
Shit
I
Want to get this one
Thank you, what the fuck get it together. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry
Oh now I can't hear you. Yeah, hang on. Oh, hey. Hi, you me
Yeah, now I can
Okay, I'm gonna show you every time you you put a video and then you take it down like sometimes. I can't hear you
I'm sorry
Thank you. I don't think she wants to watch any videos. Well, I but I mean I have to
This is it. Why do you have to? Why can't we just hang out?
We are hanging out. I'm trying to show this one. Well, this is called
the truth about Mexico
I love Mexicans, by the way
It better not be fucking racist this video. You know, they're saying they're calling
They're they're calling people tonight. They're calling the floaters on via show. So it's not that race
Loader they're saying they're like, you know, you know, like Cuban there's a big chemical they're floating in the water
Or something like that. I mean, it's so sick. Oh, you know, Vader's not gonna like that
I know he's not going to but I want to have sex with that guy baby
Vader's Cuban by the way
I love it. I love it. I'm into it. I'm gonna do that. Okay, so here it is. Okay, ready? I got it for you
You're gonna love this
Ready? I'm scared
See it's already scary
That's scary. If you think this is whining then like dude, you need to get out more. I don't know
I got a stomach full of fingernails and with a steamer on my head with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust I got a stomach full of fingernails and with his dust
the place is only white people though. What a fucking Mexico city you're from. What a fucking
thing on the low end. I hope you're demonetized. You're a good person. So like this is supposed
to disprove the pyramids? No. Oh hang on. The reason why you got from it, if you saw it, oh yeah,
okay, because you didn't remember that. But yeah, if you saw something, if you saw something, if you
No, no shade on anybody
No cultural nothing negative
But you saw something you see something
Yeah
But you saw something
More than what was shown
Ketsu Koto, right? But he was wasn't he white with a red beard and all the kind of stuff like right?
No, no, he wasn't let me look it up on
Quetzalcoatl in memory. I mean, I know he like left on a robot or something like that. He came in he took off
Talking about when the Spanish can tease the doors came, right?
Well, okay, let me know all the comic books. I mean the codexes or the oh, I mean the
Well, Quetzalcoatl it says Quetzalcoatl. I'll read it to you a little bit. It's on Wikipedia
It says Quetzalcoatl with feather serpents a dating acid culture
And literature, among the Aztecs, he was related to the wind, Venus, Sun,
merchants, arts, crafts, knowledge, and learning.
He was a Patriarch of Aztec priesthood.
He was a God of wisdom, learning, and intelligence.
One of the several foreign gods in the Aztec pantheon,
along with Teotek, Teschelopota, and Huskopoterelo.
The other two gods represented the plan of Venus and Teolok.
Ally and the god of rain. Oh, there you are teal off. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay. He wears the night around his neck the breastplate
called a
Cocodile
Spirally-volted wind jewel the talisman with a conch shell the cross section
Okay, and it says worship. Oh, I don't know if I'm where he was redheaded says it comes from the name precious serpent. Oh
depictions
The earliest do not kind of graphic depiction of the day. He appears
Stella 19 of the Olmec set of la venta
Dated to around 900 BC a serpent rising man a person probably engaged in a shamanic ritual
Oh, they're probably not exactly a depiction of the same feathered serpent dates
He worshipped in classic and post-classic periods. It shows a continuity of symbolism feathers snakes and
Somewhere around here. It's gonna say he has a red hair and a beard. Yeah, I mean I read interpretations. Okay a military
NASA culture
Uh, myths, uh, through the exacting of the makings of Quetzalcoatl,
very somewhat, between civilization,
here's the story.
Quetzalcoatl is one of the four sons of Omitekuerekiyo
and Omaketokyo, of the four Tetzelikopas,
who presented over the four cardinal directions.
the red, blue, white, and what's the other color?
Let me see, purple, oh, gold, I'm sorry.
And then, okay, so he was a morning star,
which is being sort of Lucifer, as some people call him.
He was known as the inventor of books, the calendar,
the giver of corn, symbol of death, resurrection.
He was the patron of priests and a twin Aztec high priest,
to miscribe whom opposed human sacrifice.
Most Muslim I believe
Included cycles of the Sun's because the Sun was so important to them. You know the Sun is just so important, right?
Yeah, and so in the codex chimalon apaca
It is said that because look bottle was coerced by tesla capata to be getting drunk on
Look, are you getting me drunk like that's a lot. Oh, are we repeating the ritual or you're sacrificing at dawn rain stop it?
What what nothing you're I said, you're not gonna sacrifice me by Don are you?
No, we're gonna sacrifice everybody else. Okay, perfect
Thank God. Well, I'll show you a picture because you wanted to be away everyone's left
I think we scared everyone away, but you know what? You know why I'd be here when we were so fucking awesome
Yeah, like look at this cool picture. They look cool. This is
Scout look at this
Yeah, that's what's gonna happen to them. Yes, we're gonna sacrifice them to like some big stink
Hey, I by the way, do you know what's funny? It's not my video. So don't worry cuz you know, but what's her name?
Nicki Minaj
I'm gonna bother
Have you heard of the anaconda?
Yeah, okay. We're gonna reenact the modern day of ritual right now playing this video. Oh, yeah, she's like demonic as fuck
well
Yeah, I mean, I mean, so we're so we're the Aztecs gods
Here we go. I'm gonna show you this here
Perfect. Are you ready?
Yeah, okay. Yeah, here we go
They weren't demonic really like it was just what they believed in
Right
These girls are happy but this video is pretty much just a bunch of
Always show it, uh, surgery, yes, it's made out of me, uh, care.
You can't table a pink speaker in scope, this video is stings, um, shit.
You can't keep singing trail, I'm trying to fix that check.
Anaconda 8.
Wanna check out the red hot parody?
No?
Where's the big woody bitches?
I'm not, I'm not, um, okay, so, I'm failing, I'm failing, I'm not impressing you.
I'm trying to impress Ray.
See, I see, this is why gay people can't marry women, they can't impress women.
Only straight guys can by stupidity and gay guys can so but what did you do with JT JT did something cute, right?
What did you do that was in here? I was doing something cute right now. He is um, you know playing his game
Does he have a cute butt?
Well, like I don't know if you should judge that I mean
I'm saying do you think he has a cute butt? I do
Okay
And would you be mad at me if I looked at it just looks at it's not not in a weird way just I
Was behind in the line of the store
Why do you want to look at his butt? He's taken I know he's taken but it's okay if I look at it one time
Why don't you look at Ziggy's butt or Vader's?
I don't want to look at Ziggy's butt. I mean it looked like he looked like he could Charlotte with anorexia
I'm not interested
Thought you like emo guys. I'm not. No, I like straight guys like that are with the woman already and then she
Oh, he's he's he's a straight emo guy. I thought you liked emo. Okay. I'm sorry. Okay. I'll leave a little
Jay-z. Jay-z. You're okay. Okay
What about what about later?
What is
But is he have a slight or does Jay-z have a slight cross-eye? I really attracted that
No, he doesn't. All those other pictures are photoshopped. Oh, those are photoshopped. Oh, sorry. Okay. Here. We have a song for us
You're ready? Hold my hand. Oh
Fuck
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. You're in love it. You're in love it. I
I hate Taylor Swift
You hate Taylor Swift? Why don't you put like Sabrina Carpenter or something?
I like her too, but I'm gonna make copyright for that. Hold on. Um, hold on. I think it's a parody
Well, I get better. I don't think they have a spring of carbon or parody. I didn't know that. I think I have one for this though
Let me see. Hold on. Taylor Swift parody. I
Mean, I don't see what I was looking for. I'll put this one on but I'm looking for a different one
What about Billy Eilish? I like Billy Eilish. Billy Eilish, yeah
Yeah, okay. Well, I just want you to watch this one first. This is Taylor Swift. It's called I knew you were trouble
You like that sounds good, okay good
And there's a bald guy too in the background. It is the thing that is this here
I hate bald people. It's okay. It's okay. Okay. Are you ready?
Yeah, okay. Thank you. Hold on one second. Is there you're here?
We don't think it is to say hi.
Oh, there it is.
Here it is.
Here we go.
I was insane. I dated this Disney guy. Joe Jonas was his name, but he broke up with me.
You're just way too creepy. Plus, I found someone else. His name's Mickey.
So I wrote a song about a stupid ass. Then found this guy named John, but that was over fast.
If you don't marry me, I will pull out your teeth. You're totally crazy. No. Yes. No. Yes. Maybe.
He hit me with his guitar, and he said...
We are through, just you wait, until I write a song about you
Then I met that dick, Jillian Haldick, and was obsessed right away
You've sent me 1,000 messages, and that's just from today
Oh, that's because I'm having your baby
What? But you don't even put out
Stop questioning me, JD
I'll put you six feet underground
Whoa!
Psycho! Psycho! Psycho!
God, my dear...
I think he was 15. I bought the house next door to watch you constantly and also to make sure you never ever cheat.
OMG we are done. You are scary.
Harry was my last. That one direction freak. I taped him to my wall so he could never leave.
Someone call the police. Your inside we all threw. You're just like all the rest. What did I do to you?
So I used my stalker app to track down
I love the next song, they're right on use, their blood is my ink
Hey!
Holy crap, that nut job just bursted in!
What the hell is this?
It's a support group for all the men
You wrote songs about you bitch
What? I have not written about Harry yet
I am just planning ahead
Why are you even here anyway?
To finish you all up with my pen!
No!
Devil! Devil! Devil!
Ah! Ah!
It's true, I'm not devil!
Okay, that's enough!
You were right, she's nuts!
You are coming with us!
Wait, what? Get off of me!
I'm not crazy!
Ah! Eh!
What?
This was all a trick, we knew you would come!
So be high, you're this doctor!
You're going to an insane asylum
Based on the method your eye observed
Ow! Ow!
But they don't do assholes!
No! No!
Welcome to your new home!
You're crazy too, huh?
Yo, guys! Thanks for watching!
You there, psyche?
Hey, Harry?
Yeah, I can hear you now.
You sound far away. What?
Hello? What happened to sake you? What the fuck? Maybe I need to leave him. You know.
Come on back. Hello? Yes. Hey, I want more. I want more for you. Then you get to choose
one next. Here you go. Oh man. Are you ready? Here we go.
People's sexiest many line
Now it's time for me
To be seen as a massive creep
That is why in this video
I look like a sick pedo
And why I'm soaking
A lady like she is fresh me
My bitch gross
This video is all about me
My room five is nowhere to be seen
I'm showing off my abs and all of my tattoos
Some commercial fattign
I've got a show on every set
It's time that I show you with us
I
Yeah, I can stand dead weight in a hoodie
I can develop photography
I can hold breath and hopes of me
I can act totally crazy
I can take pictures, I'm a smartphone
I can spin a blood on my heart, my soul
This is just like American Psycho
Oh, how do I make my voice so high?
Break the windows and take the auxilium
Dog a puff, always shows, after my shows
This is the part I act romance
And cover myself in robby guts
Guess he forgot where I've been through
I look so good, it's all about me
I'm so one, that's what I say
I'm damn sick, I'm number one
Depends on how nobody wants to
Watch this weird shit
Of course they do, especially this
Check that out now
to a site and have advised them they're all medicine.
I'm taking your placent to your...
Yo guys, thanks for watching my...
Okay.
Yeah?
Everyone else left.
Oh, why are you still here?
Are you serious?
No viewers?
No, two people.
I think that's two people.
I think the thing that is when I just leave
and he was probably pretty much the only viewer.
What the fuck and it's not it's sad, you know, it's good that no well person
I think you know, I believe no well ever since brandy he would know well got together the world's gonna fucking shit
It's over. It's all over. Oh, there's JC. JC. He's telling you come to bed rain. He said it's over
Can I go can I can I go can I get in bed with you guys though? I'm a cold
Okay, just one night
I'll let's see what you guys I want to be I want to be on JC behind me and you in front of me
But I'll be wearing rescue doves
Let's see what JT says
JT okay
Okay, you're getting bad it's too late. It's the best. You better get out of here. I love you sweetheart. You're the best
Oh, you're shutting down. I'm not that JC is gonna mad at me. I don't want JC to hurt me
Okay, he said it's our password. Hey skit bed. Okay. Yeah, I'm here out. I
Don't want me insulted. I love you, right?
Go get a bow to JC JC wants to
I'm gonna play this all the way. Okay. Oh, I'm gonna put mercy
Okay, rain. I'm sorry
He's asking you to go. I love you. Give me a hug. Have a hug
Hey, it's a JC like far really really bad
Um
Like he doesn't really start like me sleeping. Okay. Okay. I get the picture. I get the picture. I get the picture
I get it. I get it. I hear it. Okay. Oh, hold on. Joe's entering. You want to talk to Joe for a second?
Who the hell is that?
Joe, you're shipply.
Eww.
Eww. This is my website.
Joe's shipply?
Yeah, he's shapely. You know, Joe, he's so shapely. Oh, there he is. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh, Joe scared. Oh my God. You scared her away, Joe. Joe, you scared her away. I didn't hear you. Turn your microphone off. I'm so sorry, Jay-Jay. I'm so sorry.
He's having my problems. I don't know Joe your two pans of mime
Do pants of arms Joe, okay? Can you hear him psyche? I don't hear me. He's just talking to the air. Can you hear me now?
No, remember when you make shadows on the wall when you're a kid like oh, there's a fucking bird flyin wee
I'm a bird. I'm a bird man
Like really who the fuck said ooh when I joined you
Why do you look like the why are you a wannabe of the Limp Fiscate guy?
Yeah, it's friend Morgan
People coming for that's fine. That's fine lady. But can we look at you so we can make fun of you like let's look at you
Oh, that's right. You won't turn your camera on so you
Because you're fucking creepy. Why would I turn it on?
I'm just saying just just if you want to make fun of other people until you turn your camera
We see how ugly you are just keep your mouth closed, baby. Go
Oh my god. Don't call me baby girl. What's up? Oh my god.
You're fucking creepy and you're bald. What the fuck? You're
fucking ugly and you're ugly but you just don't want to show
us. You're old and ugly. Oh, you think I'm bald? Under this.
You're bald. Yeah, you're bald. You were taking off your
Oh, you why excuse me? Let me take it off. Does she really want to see this?
Nobody wants to see your bald head. Thank you. Thank you. Nobody wants to see your face ugly woman
Lot of ugly women have a lot of mouth up here
My hair yeah my hat by the way you ugly bitch you don't have hair bitch
I'm just saying maybe I don't maybe I do but you're still ugly. It's still ugly shit
Right, and you're the one looking like that
No, I know I'm right. I know I'm right. You don't got to say right. I know I'm right. You don't got to say right
I know I'm right. God, man
You're not even right about anything. You've never been right about me. I was pretty right about you being hideous
You're not even like his friend. So shut the fuck up, bitch
Actually, it's like he's best friend. So get out of here. No, you're not you just showed up like what about
your fake friend
Well, and you're ugly. So what's the point? I've been there for slightly you like to the highs and lows bitch
Where have you been? No way ever show their face? Say how ugly? Oh my god. Is that what you look like?
You look like a 90-year-old
Wife or sister whatever
What you look like?
I'm not even white
I'm writing a bit of white, like what's your obsession with white people?
Oh, this bitch is, oh, man, I'm sorry girl, go ahead and say what you're gonna say,
because you will hold it, it might be your last thing you ever say, you're on your last breath.
I mean
You're a fucking
Well, look at look in the mirror. Yeah, you're over here fucking talking to a 26-year-old lady
I don't give a fuck how a jar you're a creep. So look in the fucking
Oh, you want to creep out you want to see and get more creepy I can creep
Oh hell no, by the way, please don't say hell. Please don't be rude and say it. What the hell were those shoes?
Your mom's shoes. Oh
See now you're talking about okay. I got you. I got your mom
Wow, now you're talking about moms, man.
You look just like you.
Like, I'm not trying to be rude,
but whoever lives in whoever you are, lady,
as ugly as you are,
I feel bad for your parents.
I've been here.
Why the fuck have you been nowhere?
To have an ugly kid right now.
For your mom and dad,
I feel bad to have an ugly kid like you.
Like, oh, my God, this is...
We had one chance to have sex and make a kid,
and we made this ugliest woman.
Like, wow.
You're a fucking family abortion.
Bob headed bitch
Her poor parents have to look themselves in the mirror like wow
We have one kid and she's this fucking ugly like wow we failed as parents
That's the best you could come up with
Man was pretty good actually
The fuck is that it's not me I'll tell you that it looks kind of like me except for the yellow teeth
Kind of looks like my profile, but not for that mom
Does he have like fucking cheez-its or is that his actual teeth?
No, I'm just fucking with just like you, but please don't ever let this bitch ever assault me like that again
Cuz she's the ugliest nigga on these fucking streets. Yeah, there's that
It's like you don't listen to this fake fuck
Yeah, we're listening baby. We're listening
Friends are and it's not you bitch. Oh, wow. You're his real friend never heard of you before but tonight you're
I've been here all the fucking time
Wow, never bet you but you've been
Sounds good. So your lies sound good
Like you know
And he loves me
He tells me all the time, but now he loves you. God. You're right. It's like you love this freak
Yeah, I love her and I want to have a treat with her and Jaycee
You're the creep. Oh
You're right, lady
I'm gonna get real pretty good. All the things that I could I want I want to be the I want to be the middle of it
My boy psyche where I like a fucking
Ugly lady that had one mom and one dad they born a child
And she was ugly as this. Oh, not Alex. I'm not talking about I'm talking about the person
Alex what the fuck
What's wrong with you?
Why would I do that?
What the hell?
Psychee, remember when you were born in a hospital bed. I wasn't talking to you bitch. I was talking to Psychee.
I wasn't talking to you either bitch.
What's more to another live stream?
If you like what you see today consider donating down below every little bit helps the channel grow. Thank you so much
Fuck you all I hate every fucking moment one of you
That's a good good afternoon or good evening
Whatever time it is wherever in this vast world you may or may not happen to be
Welcome once more to another live stream of IP to wiki info in conjunction with IRL news time
I am your hostess Alexandra mayors
And I'm going to keep this brief I
Decided to go live tonight to share my opinion and my thoughts on a certain life
Discuss a live streamer known as Brandon Q who I think
Has received the forgiveness of the Lord, and I think that the time is
To affiliated communities to
Grant Brandon Q a new slate very recently a channel that I follow closely has
entered into a little bit of a scandal by allowing Brandon Q to be part of the panel.
I'm, of course, referring to a live streamer known as the Cult of Psyche,
and I just want to promote the Cult of Psyche as much as possible.
I think that he is an extremely educated, insightful man,
and I think that everyone who is watching this live stream right now
should go ahead and view Cult of Psyche's channel and get to know him.
because I wholeheartedly support him.
And I, like so many others,
watched his live stream with Brandon Q.
And I think that these IP2 affiliated communities
have him all wrong.
I don't think there is any evidence
of Brandon Q being a pedophile.
and anything that you bring my way,
I will wholeheartedly reject it.
Like I said, a cult of psyche entered into
a significant amount of scandal
by having Brandon Q on his panel.
And my thoughts on that are that
cult of psyche is a very good person,
extremely so.
And, you know, based on the people that I support, and I consider myself to be a very
good judge of character, I make sure to throw my weight in my support behind only the best
people.
For instance, I've not made any secret about how much I support Big T, aka Controla, aka
Carissa.
I've been watching many of her live streams where she goes through her reflection journals
I wholeheartedly support anyone who is a Christian.
Some false-minded, limp, fit, looking after you.
In fact, if you want nothing to do with God,
I don't really think that I want to have anything to do with you.
That's just my opinion.
I'm allowed to have it.
I'm allowed to have an opinion.
I know that this is going to be a very controversial position.
And he's a young man that likes to enjoy his youth and maybe others, other youths.
But I don't think that he's a pedophile.
There are many in these communities that are making these allegations and accusations on
him.
And I don't think it is right to unjustly villainize someone, especially with something
as serious as an allegation of pedophilia.
would never falsely accuse people of pedophilia.
I would never make that kind of claim without proof.
I just think that Brandon Q is being a young,
hetero-Latino male.
And I think it's time for these communities
to give him a second chance.
Of course, I know that there have been people
that have been leaving their responses,
to my opinion,
Ganville.
Now Ganvel, I want to make something very clear to you. I have not watched your live streams in quite some time
I recall watching your live streams long ago in the past
and I thoroughly enjoyed masturbating to it.
That was a long time ago,
and I don't really remember much of the content that you have.
I think that the only reason
that you're coming after Brandon Q is for attention.
I think you are acting out of vanity and greed.
If you want my opinion of Gamble,
I believe that he peaked quite a long time ago.
and now he needs attention for his channel,
not only for validation, but for donations.
And it's really quite sad that you need to unjustly villainize someone without any proof.
I believe that Gamble has lied extensively on Brandon Q.
I don't think he can produce any evidence that Brandon Q is a pedophile.
I believe that Gamble has also levied those accusations on Zeya as well.
I know that Gamble has levied the accusations of pedophilia against Zeya and said that Zeya
And I am aware that at one point he did express romantic interest with a 16-year-old girl and then proceeded to speak to her repeatedly and then have her come over to his home to live with him.
But I believe that Zaya is in a FIBA file. Maybe at one point he was in a FIBA file.
But is he a pedophile for speaking to a 16 year old girl?
Sexually. No, I don't think it is. Maybe he was in a FIBA file at one point
just like
perhaps Brandon Q was in a FIBA file at one point, but that doesn't mean he was a pedophile
So Gamble, I encourage you to just
Stay in your lane. I think that you have an over-inflated sense of your own opinion and
Ultimately, no one really cares about it
There's somebody else that I must address. I am aware also that Trisha Licious has made a live stream on me
There were a lot of different things that she said that I don't really want to address right now
But one thing that really upset me is when she was bashing me for my Christian faith
I am a deeply devoutly Christian woman. You will find that on my main channel
I have still been conducting my daily reading of the Bible
And I'm deeply insulted when somebody questions it.
So I ask you, Tricia, I have been very supportive of you.
And I've given you all my support on all my live streams.
And I think that you are doing a great job as a mother,
but do not.
Do not come for my Christian. It was I myself
Have been a victim of unjustified persecution. I am a black woman and I do believe that Brandon Q was being attacked unjustly
Really for anybody who has an opinion on anything that I have to say I just want you to understand that
Chat is not real to me
None of you are real
Your opinion doesn't matter to me
Do you see, I am God is level.
I have reached celebrity of heights
that you will not possibly comprehend.
None of you are real.
I have the word of God to back me up.
I have the Lord on my side.
Your opinion doesn't hurt me in any way.
It doesn't phase me.
Most of you, a lot of you are just racist,
just attacking me because I'm a black woman.
You hate all of the opinions that I have.
Only specifically because I'm a black woman. Okay. I think that this live stream has come to an end
Brandon Q by the way will now be
Allowed into my panel whenever I have an open panel
Brandon Q was allowed in my chat if I've previously
blocked Brandon Q
He is now unblocked and if you have anything to say about that
Why don't you just go ahead and go to Marshall's, or Michael's, or Home Depot, and just buy
a rope, and then just come find me, and then what you can do is that you can tie the rope
into a noose, and then you can come find me, and then just put the noose around my neck,
Because I know that's what a lot of you want to do.
It'll be easy to get away with murdering a black woman nowadays.
I don't know who this is.
You can get away with it.
You can get away with killing me.
If you have a problem with my opinion, you can just lynch me.
Everyone have a good night.
Make sure to read your Bibles thoroughly.
Make sure to praise God and remember you are nothing compared to me.
Have a good night.
Good night, psyche. Good night, Brandon
Donating to my cash
Thank you so much
She was on my show. So this is woman. She's one of my biggest donators. She's one of the founders of the show
That's a woman
Yeah, that's a woman. Yeah, she was in the porn industry. She played the she played the mom of the Cosby show porn
Yeah, that's a woman right there. I'll show you her when she's on my show. Do you want to see when she called me the n-word?
That was a good show
Are you interested?
JT are you here?
Well, JT is asking who this person is. Oh, I was under mayors
Have you heard of I was under mayors? She's a huge celebrity
I'll be you know, it's the Alexander mayors. I'm not kidding. I asked because I don't know any of these people
The Alexander mayor the like the one there's only one only Monica Foster, you know
the big cheese
You haven't heard of her. Where have you even been or a rock?
Yeah, I have actually I'm so sorry. Okay. Well, I can show you a little bit of her
You want to see a little bit of her? I have a little bit of her on tape
I'm a fucking turtle. I live under a rock. I'm sorry. Hey, it's okay. Hey gg
You know we're gonna cut it in get in get in rally Nancy get in here shoot. I want all everybody over here
This is Monica Foster. This is the
Here we go Monica Foster
JT says well, she looks different from what I remember. I
Don't hate any animals. I just hate see there was something at least one thing that's about you Alex
I'm trying so hard to be nice to you
Why won't you just embrace it Alex?
You're a beautiful human inside and out
You're really your porn career was very boring, but besides that you seem like a wonderful nice person
Thing wasn't for you though. It was quite a bore
Didn't watch Alex Marry porn be quite honest
No
You're a fucking over-the-hill lady who never had a child or a husband and you take out all
the frustration on random YouTubers.
That's what you do.
Apparently you just had a stroke because I can see the droopyness now that you mentioned
that you had a stroke.
I can see it.
What about like massage therapy or something?
No, you sleep next to an air conditioner
Just put the gun to your head and you sleep next to air conditioner because you can like reverse at it
No, okay. Well, it's a shame that you're you know, it's a shame, you know, you had a stroke in your face. I know
So what's your five-year plan Alex? You do you plan on always being?
You okay good good good it's important to have hobbies Alex
I know. Yeah. Bugged out. You worry about it.
I don't worry about crazy ladies on the internet. I just really don't.
I know you get off on people being scared of you though. I find that very funny.
You know
Oh, no, it's Alex mayors. Oh, everybody everybody be scared of the Alex mayor. I don't I don't know
You're not gonna get that with me sweetie, I hate to tell you
Wait, hold on you want a Nazi to knock you up really?
that that can't be true. I'm not looking at chat. I'm just
listening to you. I love Alex. I have a better communication
voice than you do, Alex. Face it. I have a better voice for
broadcasting than you do. It's too loud. Alex, I have a better
I have a better podcasting voice than you do admit it, admit it, that's fair.
I think I could tell you and get away with it.
Admit that I have a better podcast.
I've done it before.
You've killed me before.
That's interesting.
Do tell.
Listen to me, Alex.
The audience is intrigued.
They want to hear more.
Let's admit that I have a better broadcasting voice in your face. I know you think you're the best bracket. I have not you I
Am superior is as far as it comes to broadcasting voices miss Alex
Everything I know about you everything you've been told everything. I know about your location
Okay, I do tell you
Give me a state maybe
Approximate location, you know, just like you get all scared
You already are
Yeah, you get that, huh?
Give me that, I'll be really scared if you give me the approximate location.
Look how evil she got.
I just, I love it so much.
You are one of my favorite characters on YouTube.
You are.
I'm your dad.
No, you can scare like wine moms and stuff, you know, scare me.
I just think you're a sad, lonely old woman who really, unlovable, unlovable somewhere.
Careful to say
Are you my dad mommy if I was your child Alex, would you have a what do you call it a boarded me?
Well, I know his location. I know exactly what he looks like
I know his routine, I'm not Russian, I'm African American but he'd be easy, no, bring him back.
Bring him back? Okay, well Ghost is backstage too but no Ghost.
I don't want to talk to Ghost, I want to talk to...
Stop cutting the Blacks except you, Gallux, the Blacks do not accept you.
I've talked to them, I have my Black carrying card.
We talked you're not you know, we you don't you're not black
Okay, that's to my
Obclaiming black stop claiming African-American
Your your your African-American rights have been revoked. That's to my benefit continue
That's very racist of you to say that
You get out of speeding tickets now
You do know I
Know where you live, right? You said that a bunch of times, but you won't even give me in the product the location
Which makes me feel that you're full of shit
You're just upset that I have a better broadcasting voice than you do
100% 100%
Being nice to you and you're still
Right to the family like this shit does work on wine. What wine moms hasn't quite working on Steve
It does so, you know, I know everything about you. Really you know that I have
You if I want even since listening Alex the audience is listening
Give a little teaser
There's no
I have the better radio voice than you do admit that I have the better radio voice than you do Alex
You're a child Steve Pokemon wins
Inmitted
Is this flirting are you flirting with me Alex stop?
Absolutely, I'm not I can tell you that because I've watched your pornography. I found it boring
Why would you watch my pornography so unless you're okay Alex? You're a crazy person on the internet
Why wouldn't I watch your pornography?
She totally wants to fuck me
Well, okay, so we're gonna see Pokemon show every day
This shit works on the wine wine moms it does not work every single thing about you
Do you really make a movie including the sides of my way, huh? Oh, sweetie
Kiss kiss, huh? That's about what four inches. Yeah
Look at his smile on her face.
I lost it in your face.
You're not attracted.
I'm adorable.
I've had many, many people, some of these communities tell me I'm adorable.
I actually look like, he looks like...
if Steven Seagal were to have been punched in the face
and nobody were to have repaired the...
He just couldn't afford the surgery to fix it.
Pretty good.
Yeah, that video is too long.
I can't hear anybody.
I'm back.
what the hell was that? what the hell was that?
nothing? i'm so sorry rain i'm so sorry rain rain
you're you're traumatizing me i'm so sorry i'm too innocent for this
i know so am i i am too
You can't imagine what's happening to you in this community. No, you can't imagine but okay, we'll finish it up
Oh, I just want to show you the rest of this. This is you'll love it. You'll love it
This is so good rain. You're here with me JT
Get out cut a love. Can you tell the JT to cut a love? I won't touch
I miss I'm gonna enter the bed watching but just imagine my eyes just peeking over the
edge of the downy comfort
JT okay
Did he I think he went back to his game. He went to bed. Okay. Oh, you're good. Oh
I'm a little bit drunk. I'm so sorry. You're often and I was finished up here
There we go. You like this. This is good. Oh
Look like
Yeah, I know I know everything about you. I'm adorable
Absolutely adorable, Alex.
Disgusting. You're disgusting.
And you're short.
I've been told I look exactly like my dog, if I'm being quite honest with you.
How can you call a dog disgusting?
A dog would be better looking than you.
Look at that. That's a beautiful dog.
I'm not a canine person.
You're not a human.
You're not an animal person in general.
Yeah, you're into the world.
You don't really like animals, do you?
She does not the way that you're unlovable. You're not capable of giving or receiving love
You've proven this over and over again throughout your entire life
100% 100% I've been
Amazingly not
But you are somebody who's a very hateful individual, who basically never could have been conceived.
You're somebody who never should have been born.
You're somebody who aesthetically is not very attractive.
Your point is disgusting.
You're somebody who has to go all the internet without showing their face because you're not good at it.
You know why I don't show my face? Because you're a loser because you're an ass.
I don't show my face because I'm crazy people like you.
Who ever should have been conceived? Somebody who never should have been born.
That is your reality. You pathetic.
Little piece of shit, where if I ever could kick your ass in the face, I would do it without
having to take it.
That was 6 foot 5.
That is the reality of you.
Look how dramatic that was.
And you can go on and on and on and on like krypton, but no matter where you are.
And you can go on and on and on and on and on like krypton, but no matter where you are.
And you can go on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and
on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and
What? It doesn't have to do with race, it doesn't have to do with clack, it doesn't have to do with anything, it doesn't have to do with your being, you're a literal piece of the artist who never said it before, and the sooner that you can put a god damn gun to your head.
I thought you were supposed to put a gun in my head.
I will.
Finally be happy
I just want to put a gun to your own face right between
I've already seen what you look like.
You said that numerous times.
You were that short.
You're approved of that.
You have very strange eyes to be honest with you, and then it makes me wonder what's your mother right?
Your mother was a
day after day.
I wasn't joining those, Lisa.
I was trying to figure it out,
but then we figured it out
and we're like, oh, this four
unimportant souls.
Look at you, you hear my radio
voice and you're squirming in your
seat.
Or is this a rape victim all spring?
My broad passing, boys, is make you try to stimulate your clip
by moving like that.
You can't fool me, woman.
Well, it was also R.D. Dog.
He scans more rape, gang, victim.
That is who you are, the rape, gang, victim.
That's why you call yourself a dog.
Maybe it's just rape time.
You're unlovable.
Alex. Yep, you are a rape victim of rape. A rape offspring, a rape gang offspring. That's you.
You're just a horrible person. Inside of that, I love it. You are a rape gang offspring. I was being
nice to Richard too, but this is where we're at. You are a rape gang offspring. It's not through
Rapist men, rapist dogs, I mean, can I have a shake's curtain off?
Oh, I want a shake's curtain off!
Yes, that is the reality of the army.
Oh, uh, I don't know what it would be.
A pit bull.
A pit bull raped his mother.
Oh, now it's a dog?
A dog?
Right, he made it.
And that's why he looks like he has.
You know, he has.
True colors shine through, we can see your true colors, that's why we love you, he's a werewolf, he's a teen wolf I guess, teen wolf, some sort of a fun game.
of a canine all spring, well, that's how we got the,
well, what do they call them, big foot?
Werewolves?
That's what they are.
He's a big foot.
Everyone will wonder about it.
Oh, a big foot.
But that's what he is, is because of the rape gang.
Because of the rape gang.
I owe my life to that rape gang.
A canine!
Yeah, that's it. Look how fucking insane you are. You have to wake up every morning.
Look at how insane you are. He's a fucking insane.
Look in the mirror and be like, holy shit in my entire life.
All you have to do is consult the people over at Guy in TV.
Skim Walker Ranch.
Let's not be showered, Alex. We do know you have the autism.
Not too great with the personal hygiene. Got you kicked out of porn industry. We know that.
That doesn't even make any sense.
All of it sure would make complete sense.
I know you're a part of the rape game.
It's called Vagicill, Alex. Vagicill.
Yeah, you're somehow mentally deficient.
I mean, I'm such a woman who is on so many levels.
Above you.
Have I read your voice better than your radio voice?
Admitted.
You're just mad that my radio voice is better than yours.
That's why you're mad.
I have a true broadcasting voice, Alex.
You're such a shit.
You're sounding like a photo of, like...
Old fashioned weirdos from another time that never showed up.
Oh, I thought it was a re-victim, or my mom was.
Well, your mom definitely should not have conceived you, yes.
Well, I mean, thank God you won't be ever conceived, right?
Thank the Lord for that.
Oh, I've already been conceived, but you've never shown up.
No, you will not conceive.
Meaning you will have any children to pass on your mental illness.
Oh, I'm so sure.
You absolutely cannot, don't lie to the folks out there, you cannot conceive, cannot have
children, your uterus is trying up, don't lie to the people, you can't is because you're
undesirable.
I like, I'm going to see him a few more times, you are very distressed, your nose alone as, and you pass as a baby, no, I've seen you, you pass as Caucasian, but your nose, strangely, it screams a tube, it screams a tube, it's wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong.
It's I think you're are you actually black passing us white? Is that what it is?
Got me folks. I do go by black rg
When I saw your picture
See this again
This is why I say
I had the black card Alex you could not claim black
It is no we do not accept you
Oh, well, he's admitting that he's a nigger. Good.
Okay. Excellent.
His nose.
I've never seen a nose as long as this person.
His nose is literally like...
Did you try to say you got a nigger nose?
Well, you are a nigger without doubt.
I finally got it, Jay.
I'm very happy.
I've never seen a face as ugly as yours.
I'm adorable.
The 10 times.
Blaming.
No, you're not adorable.
You're passing us one.
So adorable.
But you're very ugly.
I'm passing
You're a solid you're always talking about how wonderful your voice is mine is so much better
You're a solid nigger, yes
Can you sing endless love for us? Why would I do anything? You're obviously a lot of me obviously
I don't know what you're talking about. You're just a solid, white trash nigger.
You think I couldn't sing true colors? I certainly can't sing that.
Well, you're a solid, white trash nigger of nigger, white trash...
I'm actually going to be like an elementary kid. Cut it out.
I'm not interested. I've seen you fuck Alex. I'm not interested.
Well, I don't know what you're looking up, but you're a solid white
Looking at your porn and I'm telling you cannot fuck
But you're a solid white trash nigger and your mother is a solid white trash nigger as
Solid not white trash nigger. You're of nigger sock. That's all you are
Amazing don't
You never, you never see who amazes me.
You always deliver the good.
Who never should have been conceived,
never should have been born,
should have been exterminated,
probably.
With the Jews, right?
With the rest of the Jews?
Exactly.
See, I'm glad we're on the same page.
Yes, we are.
Yeah, okay